export const commonThingsQuiz = {
  quizInfo: {
    description:
      'Test your knowledge of common items with Common Things Quiz! This interactive quiz game challenges players to identify everyday objects based on images. With a variety of questions spanning from household items to everyday tools, players will put their observation skills to the test. To play, simply click "Start Quiz" and begin answering questions. Each question presents an image of an object along with multiple-choice options. Choose the correct answer by clicking on the corresponding button.',
    title: "Common Things 1",
  },
  quizQuestions: [
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for Cat?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Cat.svg",
      choices: ["ほん", "くつ", "かさ", "ねこ"],
      correctAnswer: "ねこ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for book?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Book.svg",
      choices: ["みずとり", "みず", "ほん", "みずく"],
      correctAnswer: "ほん",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for flower?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Flower.svg",
      choices: ["はな", "みず", "みずとり", "みずく"],
      correctAnswer: "はな",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for dog?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Dog.svg",
      choices: ["みずとり", "いぬ", "みず", "みずく"],
      correctAnswer: "いぬ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for tea?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Tea.svg",
      choices: ["みずとり", "みずく", "ほんや", "おちゃ"],
      correctAnswer: "おちゃ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for umbrella?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Umbrella.svg",
      choices: ["みずとり", "みず", "かさ", "みずく"],
      correctAnswer: "かさ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for car?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Car.svg",
      choices: ["みずとり", "みず", "くるま", "みずく"],
      correctAnswer: "くるま",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for apple?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Apple.svg",
      choices: ["りんご", "みず", "かさ", "にんじん"],
      correctAnswer: "りんご",
    },

    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for school?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/School.svg",
      choices: ["すいか", "がっこう", "おちゃ", "くつした"],
      correctAnswer: "がっこう",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for pen?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Pen.svg",
      choices: ["はな", "えんぴつ", "くるま", "ほんや"],
      correctAnswer: "えんぴつ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for fish?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Fish.svg",
      choices: ["さかな", "みずとり", "かさ", "いぬ"],
      correctAnswer: "さかな",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for chair?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Chair.svg",
      choices: ["おちゃ", "いす", "くつした", "りんご"],
      correctAnswer: "いす",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for watch?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Watch.svg",
      choices: ["すいか", "くつ", "とけい", "かさ"],
      correctAnswer: "とけい",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for rice?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Rice.svg",
      choices: ["はな", "ごはん", "えんぴつ", "くるま"],
      correctAnswer: "ごはん",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for mountain?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Mountain.svg",
      choices: ["くつした", "やま", "ほんや", "みず"],
      correctAnswer: "やま",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for phone?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Phone.svg",
      choices: ["かさ", "てがみ", "でんわ", "いぬ"],
      correctAnswer: "でんわ",
    },
  ],
};

export const commonThingsQuiz2 = {
  quizInfo: {
    description:
      'Test your knowledge of common items with Common Things Quiz! This interactive quiz game challenges players to identify everyday objects based on images. With a variety of questions spanning from household items to everyday tools, players will put their observation skills to the test. To play, simply click "Start Quiz" and begin answering questions. Each question presents an image of an object along with multiple-choice options. Choose the correct answer by clicking on the corresponding button.',
    title: "Common Things 2",
  },
  quizQuestions: [
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for table?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Table.svg",
      choices: ["つくえ", "ねこ", "かさ", "みず"],
      correctAnswer: "つくえ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for computer?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Computer.svg",
      choices: ["コンピュータ", "くるま", "ほんや", "ねこ"],
      correctAnswer: "コンピュータ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for bread?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Bread.svg",
      choices: ["ぱん", "かさ", "くつ", "りんご"],
      correctAnswer: "ぱん",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for chair?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Chair.svg",
      choices: ["いす", "はな", "ほんや", "すいか"],
      correctAnswer: "いす",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for television?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Television.svg",
      choices: ["テレビ", "さかな", "くるま", "おちゃ"],
      correctAnswer: "テレビ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for juice?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Juice.svg",
      choices: ["ジュース", "みず", "ほんや", "いす"],
      correctAnswer: "ジュース",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for clock?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Clock.svg",
      choices: ["とけい", "くつした", "りんご", "ねこ"],
      correctAnswer: "とけい",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for bicycle?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Bicycle.svg",
      choices: ["じてんしゃ", "かさ", "すいか", "つくえ"],
      correctAnswer: "じてんしゃ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for pencil?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Pencil.svg",
      choices: ["えんぴつ", "かさ", "ほんや", "いぬ"],
      correctAnswer: "えんぴつ",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese word for map?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Map.svg",
      choices: ["ちず", "ねこ", "くるま", "おちゃ"],
      correctAnswer: "ちず",
    },
  ],
};

export const foodQuiz = {
  quizInfo: {
    title: "Japanese Food Quiz",
    description:
      "Test your knowledge of various foods with Japanese Food Quiz! This interactive quiz game challenges players to identify different food items based on images and their Japanese names. From fruits and vegetables to snacks and desserts, players will put their Japanese food vocabulary to the test. To play, simply click 'Start Quiz' and begin answering questions. Each question presents an image of a food item along with multiple-choice options in Japanese. Choose the correct answer by clicking on the corresponding button.",
  },
  quizQuestions: [
    {
      question: "What is this fruit in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Apple.svg",
      choices: ["りんご", "バナナ", "オレンジ", "ぶどう"],
      correctAnswer: "りんご", // Apple
    },
    {
      question: "What is this vegetable in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Carrot.svg",
      choices: ["にんじん", "ブロッコリー", "トマト", "きゅうり"],
      correctAnswer: "にんじん", // Carrot
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say bread in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Bread.svg",
      choices: ["やさい", "ぱん", "にく", "たまご"],
      correctAnswer: "ぱん", // ぱん (Bread)
    },

    {
      question: "How do you say tea in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Tea.svg",
      choices: ["おちゃ", "こーひー", "じゅーす", "みず"],
      correctAnswer: "おちゃ", // Tea
    },

    {
      question: "What is this vegetable in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Corn.svg",
      choices: ["とうもろこし", "アーティチョーク", "ネギ", "オクラ"],
      correctAnswer: "とうもろこし", // Corn
    },
    {
      question: "What is this fruit in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Strawberry.svg",
      choices: ["いちご", "ばなな", "みかん", "ぶどう"],
      correctAnswer: "いちご", // Strawberry
    },
    {
      question: "What is this item in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Bento.svg",
      choices: ["おにぎり", "べんとう", "おでん", "すし"],
      correctAnswer: "べんとう", // Bentou (Box Lunch)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say sushi in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Sushi.svg",
      choices: ["おにぎり", "べんとう", "おでん", "すし"],
      correctAnswer: "すし", // すし (Sushi)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say eel in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Eel.svg",
      choices: ["ほたて", "さけ", "うなぎ", "たい"],
      correctAnswer: "うなぎ", // うなぎ (Eel)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say Ramen in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Ramen.svg",
      choices: ["そば", "うどん", "ラーメン", "おにぎり"],
      correctAnswer: "ラーメン", // ラーメン (Ramen)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say fish in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Fish2.svg",
      choices: ["さかな", "にく", "やさい", "ごはん"],
      correctAnswer: "さかな", // さかな (Fish)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say egg in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Egg.svg",
      choices: ["おやつ", "ごはん", "たまご", "やさい"],
      correctAnswer: "たまご", // たまご (Egg)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say salt in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Salt.svg",
      choices: ["みず", "あげる", "しお", "さとう"],
      correctAnswer: "しお", // しお (Salt)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say watermelon in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/watermelon.svg",
      choices: ["すいか", "なす", "きゅうり", "れんこん"],
      correctAnswer: "すいか", // すいか (Watermelon)
    },
    {
      question: "How do you say potato in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/potato.svg",
      choices: ["たまねぎ", "じゃがいも", "にんじん", "れんこん"],
      correctAnswer: "じゃがいも", // じゃがいも (Potato)
    },
  ],
};

export const foodQuizJapanese2 = {
  quizInfo: {
    title: "Japanese Food Quiz",
    description:
      "Test your knowledge of various foods with Japanese Food Quiz! This interactive quiz game challenges players to identify different food items based on images and their Japanese names. From fruits and vegetables to snacks and desserts, players will put their Japanese food vocabulary to the test. To play, simply click 'Start Quiz' and begin answering questions. Each question presents an image of a food item along with multiple-choice options in Japanese. Choose the correct answer by clicking on the corresponding button.",
  },
  quizQuestions: [
    {
      question: "What is this fruit in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Fruit1.svg",
      choices: ["りんご", "バナナ", "オレンジ", "ぶどう"],
      correctAnswer: "りんご", // Apple
    },
    {
      question: "What is this vegetable in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Vegetable1.svg",
      choices: ["にんじん", "ブロッコリー", "トマト", "きゅうり"],
      correctAnswer: "にんじん", // Carrot
    },
    {
      question: "What is this snack in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Snack1.svg",
      choices: ["ポップコーン", "チョコレート", "プレッツェル", "チップス"],
      correctAnswer: "ポップコーン", // Popcorn
    },
    {
      question: "What is this dessert in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Dessert1.svg",
      choices: ["ケーキ", "アイスクリーム", "クッキー", "ドーナツ"],
      correctAnswer: "アイスクリーム", // Ice Cream
    },
    {
      question: "これは何ですか？",
      img: "/assets/quiz/おちゃ.svg",
      choices: ["おちゃ", "こーひー", "じゅーす", "みず"],
      correctAnswer: "おちゃ", // Tea
    },
    {
      question: "What is this fruit in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Fruit2.svg",
      choices: ["パイナップル", "キウイ", "スイカ", "いちご"],
      correctAnswer: "パイナップル", // Pineapple
    },

    {
      question: "What is this dessert in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Dessert2.svg",
      choices: ["ブラウニー", "カップケーキ", "チーズケーキ", "プリン"],
      correctAnswer: "カップケーキ", // Cupcake
    },
    {
      question: "What is this fruit in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Fruit3.svg",
      choices: ["マンゴー", "梨", "さくらんぼ", "グレープフルーツ"],
      correctAnswer: "マンゴー", // Mango
    },
    {
      question: "What is this vegetable in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Vegetable3.svg",
      choices: ["ズッキーニ", "大根", "じゃがいも", "アスパラガス"],
      correctAnswer: "ズッキーニ", // Zucchini
    },

    {
      question: "What is this fruit in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Fruit4.svg",
      choices: ["ブルーベリー", "ざくろ", "メロン", "いちじく"],
      correctAnswer: "ブルーベリー", // Blueberry
    },
    {
      question: "What is this vegetable in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Vegetable4.svg",
      choices: ["とうもろこし", "アーティチョーク", "ネギ", "オクラ"],
      correctAnswer: "とうもろこし", // Corn
    },
    {
      question: "What is this snack in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Snack4.svg",
      choices: [
        "プレッツェルスティック",
        "レーズン",
        "ひまわりの種",
        "チーズパフ",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "ひまわりの種", // Sunflower Seeds
    },
    {
      question: "What is this dessert in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Dessert4.svg",
      choices: ["タルト", "カンノーロ", "ムース", "フラン"],
      correctAnswer: "カンノーロ", // Cannoli
    },
    {
      question: "What is this drink in Japanese?",
      img: "/assets/quiz/Drink4.svg",
      choices: [
        "アイスティー",
        "ホットチョコレート",
        "ミルクシェイク",
        "フルーツパンチ",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "ミルクシェイク", // Milkshake
    },
  ],
};
